admango.com 2016-06-06

# 

                                                   admanGo’s Data Privacy Statement
This Statement is made by admanGo.com Limited in accordance with the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance of the Hong Kong Special
Administrative Region ("the Ordinance"). The Statement is intended to notify you why personal data is collected, how it will be used
and to whom data access requests are to be addressed.
1.     Personal data will only be collected for a lawful purpose, and by lawful and fair means. The purpose for which your personal data
       and other information may be used include:
       a. the provision and daily operation (including without limitation, maintenance and administration) of the online application and
       data services provided to you;
       b. incorporation into our database, analysis, research and auditing;
       c. prevention or detection of crime and copyright infringement;
       d. legal proceedings; and
       e. other purposes directly relating to the activities identified above.
2. Personal data provided by you will not be kept longer than is necessary for the fulfilment of the purpose for which it is collected.
     As a general rule the maximum retention period is 7 years.
3. If you log in to our Services using your Facebook ID, we receive basic personal data from your social network profile. The scope of
     details we receive depends on your social network account privacy settings; however, they might include your social network ID,
     public profile information and email address. If you wish to change the scope of your social network profile information that we
     receive upon your registration, you should review the privacy policy or other guidance available on your social network’s website
     and change your privacy settings.
4. If you log in to our Services using Instagram ID, we will not receive any personal data from your social network profile. Your
     Instagram ID will only be used to request Instagram data from Instagram’s API, and it will not be stored or cached in any admanGo’
     servers.
5. Personal data except Instagram ID supplied to admanGo will reside in admanGo servers which are protected to the maximum
     possible extent against unauthorized or accidental access, processing, erasure or other illegitimate manipulation. admanGo
     servers are, to the maximum possible extent, protected against security attacks over the Internet by means of system securities
     set up and the "Firewalls". A well-organized and safe system of backups is in place.
6. All reasonably practicable steps will be taken to ensure that personal data held are protected against unauthorized or accidental
     access, processing, erasure or other use.
7. Your personal data and other information shall be kept confidential. admanGo may, at its sole discretion and for the purpose(s)
     mentioned above, provide your personal data and other information to:
     a. any person under a duty of confidentiality to admanGo or who has given to admanGo an undertaking of confidentiality; and
     b. any person or regulatory or other authority to whom we are under an obligation or duty to make disclosure pursuant to any
     relevant laws, rules, regulations, codes or guidelines binding on admanGO.
8. Under and in accordance with the terms of the Ordinance, you have the right to:
     a. check whether admanGo holds your personal data and right of access to such data;
     b. require admanGo to correct any data relating to you which is inaccurate; and
     c. ascertain admanGo’s policies and procedures in relation to data and to be informed of the kind of personal data held by
     admanGo.
9. You have the right to access and update your information and contact us. If you have any question about our Privacy Policy
     Statement, please write to us at:
     admanGo Limited, 1101, 50 Gloucester Road, Wanchai, Hong Kong
